var state = {
  questions: [
    {
      question:
        "Which of these explosives was first patented in 1898 by German chemist Georg Friedrich Henning and first used in World War II?",
      answers: ["HMX", "RDX", "TNT", "PETN"],
      correctAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Among the Following, whom does the Indian Constitution permit to take part in the Proceedings of Parliament?",
      answers: [
        "Solicitor General",
        "Attorney General",
        "Cabinet Secretary",
        "Chief Justice",
      ],
      correctAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following forts was not built by the European colonial powers in India?",
      answers: [
        "Fort Dansborg",
        "Fort Naarden",
        "Fort Chambray",
        "Fort Santa Katherina",
      ],
      correctAnswer: 2,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which colonial power ended its involvement in India by selling the rights of the Nicobar Islands to the British on October 18, 1868?",
      answers: ["Belgium", " Italy ", "Denmark", "France"],
      correctAnswer: 2,
    },
    {
      question:
        " Who is the first woman to successfully climb K2, the world’s second highest mountain peak?",
      answers: [
        "Junko Tabei",
        "Wanda Rutkiewicz",
        "Tamae Watanabe",
        "CHantal Mauduit",
      ],
      correctAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Who, in 1978, became the first person to be born in the continent of Antarctica?",
      answers: [
        "Emilio Palma",
        "James Weddell",
        "Juan Pablo ",
        "Charles Wilkes",
      ],
      correctAnswer: 0,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Who commanded the ‘Hector’, the first British trading ship to land at Surat?",
      answers: [
        "Paul Canning",
        "William Hawkins",
        "Thomas Roe",
        "James Lancaster",
      ],
      correctAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What was the name given to the supercluster of galaxies, discovered by ateam of Indian astronomers in 2017?",
      answers: ["Laxmi", "Parvati", "Saraswati", "Durga"],
      correctAnswer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: `Who is credited for coining the term 'Meghalaya'`,
      answers: [
        "Bankim Chandra Chatterjee",

        "Shiba Prasad Chatterjee",

        "Radhanath Sikdar",

        "Dorothy Middleton",
      ],
      correctAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Launched in 1817, which of these ships built by the Wadia Group in Bombay is the oldest British warship still afloat?",
      answers: [
        "HMS Minden",
        "HMS Cornwallis",
        "HMS Trincomalee",
        "HMS Meanee",
      ],
      correctAnswer: 2,
    },
  ],

  currentQuestion: 0,
  userScore: 0,
  userAnswers: [],
};
